

#### **PROFILE**

Innovative, optimized solution seeker. Excited to be at the deployment phase of my new career as a Full-stack web developer. I am ambitious, adventurous, assiduous, animated, and an alliteration advocate.

My work experience has given me the knowledge and skills to quickly adapt to changing circumstances and continue achieving the best performance.

### PHONE:

+91 8092766575

### shubham14p3@gmail.com

**PORTFOLIO** 

## **HACKERRANK**

**GITHUB** 

# LINKEDIN

# SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking

#### **AWARDS**

- Best Employer of the Year
- Techfest Coder

### PERSONAL INFO

### Address:

H. No-21, Radha Kunj, Jyoti Nagar,Radhika Nagar, Kharangajhar, Telco,Jamshedpur, Jharkhand, India - 831004

# **SHUBHAM RAJ**

## FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### **SKILLS**

Front-End: JavaScript, React, Redux, ¡Query, HTML5, CSS3

Back-End: Ruby, Rails, RSpec, MySQL

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, TDD, Mobile/Responsive

Development, Chrome Dev Tools

**Professional:** Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork, Mentoring

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Full Stack Developer**

Gammastack, Indore

05-2020-continuing

- Developing a ReactJS based application and working in NextJS.
- Working in MERN Stack development.
- Learning new Front-End Web Technologies like NextJS & Typescript

## **Full Stack Developer**

Dashclicks, Jaipur

04-2020-05-2020

- Developed a ReactJS based application and worked in NodeJS.
- Worked as MERN Stack development
- Learned new front-end technologies and implemented them

# **Front End Developer**

Datamites Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore

08-2019 - 04-2020

- Engaged in client communication for all-important.
- Performed Data cleansing/transformation, feature engineering.
- Developed and implemented advanced analytics approaches.

# **Software Engineer**

Nagravision India Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore

07-2018 - 07-2019

- System Acceptance Testing and Program delivery.
- Reporting Tests and Technical documentation.
- Implemented STB automated test lab environments.

# **PROJECTS**

- **Inncodesolutions** Hosting Website Solution created on React.
- **Fillurbasket** E-commerce Website created on React.
- **Techno-Article** Article website created with Ruby on Rails.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Microverse

Remote Full Stack Web Development Program

Feb 2020 – Continuing

- Spent 1300+ hours mastering algorithms, data structures, and full-stack development while simultaneously developing projects with Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, and Redux.
- Developed skills in remote pair-programming using GitHub, industrystandard gitflow, and daily standups to communicate and collaborate with international remote developers

#### **Bhilai Institute of Technology**

Bachelor in Engineering with Computer Science Engineering 2014-2018

- Followed my passion in Software Development and completed Bachelor Engineering in Computer Science & Engineering.
- Represented my College in many national and domestic events.

# Vidya Bharati Chinmaya Vidyalaya

10 + 2 with Science

2001 - 2014

 President of Vidya Bharati Chinmaya Vidyalaya, facilitated monthly meetings to enhance a diverse community. Managed activities like monthly talks, workshops, and student panels.